const tough = [
  {
    question: "Who coined the word 'New England'?",
    answers: {
      a: "King James I",
      b: "John Smith",
      c: "Thomas Hooker",
      d: "Paul Revere"
    },
    correctAnswer: "b"
  },
  {
    question: "Coulrophobia means fear of what?",
    answers: {
      a: "Clowns",
      b: "old people",
      c: "Sacred things",
      d: "Antarctica"
    },
    correctAnswer: "a"
  },
  {
    question: 'Which author wrote the novel "Catch-22"?',
    answers: {
      a: "JD Salinger",
      b: "Kurt Vonnegut",
      c: "James Joyce",
      d: "Joseph Heller"
    },
    correctAnswer: "d"
  },
  {
    question: "Pythagoras' Theorem is a theorem concerning which shape?",
    answers: {
      a: "Polyhedron",
      b: "Right triangle",
      c: "Octagon",
      d: "Equilateral triangle"
    },
    correctAnswer: "b"
  },
  {
    question: "The Alaskans have at least how many words for snow?",
    answers: {
      a: "12",
      b: "25",
      c: "8",
      d: "50"
    },
    correctAnswer: "d"
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which singer wrote the State Farm 'Like a Good Neighbor' jingle?",
    answers: {
      a: "An unknown writer",
      b: "Barry Manilow",
      c: "Rod Stewart",
      d: "Luther Vandross"
    },
    correctAnswer: "b"
  },
  {
    question:
      "Sleeping through winter is hibernation, while sleeping through summer is __:",
    answers: {
      a: "A good idea",
      b: "Defenestration",
      c: "A waste of a perfectly good summer",
      d: "Estivation"
    },
    correctAnswer: "d"
  },
  {
    question: "Eight of the ten largest statues in the world depict __:",
    answers: {
      a: "US Presidents",
      b: "Ghandi",
      c: "Abe Lincoln",
      d: "Buddha"
    },
    correctAnswer: "d"
  },
  {
    question: "All swans in England __:",
    answers: {
      a: "Are endangered",
      b: "Are white",
      c: "Are owned by the Queen",
      d: "Are tagged"
    },
    correctAnswer: "c"
  },
  {
    question: "Male students enrolled at Brigham Young University __:",
    answers: {
      a: "Need a doctor's note to grow a beard.",
      b: "Are required to keep their nails short.",
      c: "Are separated from female students.",
      d: "Must become priests."
    },
    correctAnswer: "a"
  }
];
